Wow! You look nice. What's the occasion?
穿這麼帥要去哪裡？
Monica and I are celebrating our 10-month anniversary.
摩妮卡和我要慶祝滿十個月
Got reservations at Jean-George.
我們在喬治法國餐廳訂了位置
How'd you get in?
你們怎麼進得去？
Made a few calls, pulled some strings...
打了幾通電話，動用一些關係
...and they'll seat us if we both have chicken and don't get dessert.
如果我們都吃雞，不叫甜點 就讓我們11：30進去吃
-Hi,Chandler. -Hey,Caitlin.
錢德 凱特琳
Somebody got a haircut.
新髮型喔
I hate it. I look like an 8-year-old boy.
我恨死了，活像八歲小男孩
If that was true, gym class would've been more interesting.
如果真的是這樣 那以前上體育課會有趣許多
-It's $27 even. -Okay. Here you go.
正好27美元 好，給你
Where's the chicken?
你養的雞呢？
It's in the back. The duck pissed him off.
在後頭，被這鴨子氣跑了
He said that eggs came first.
鴨子說先有蛋，才有雞
-Thanks. I'll see you later. -Bye.
謝了，下回見 好，再見
What the hell was that?
你那樣算是什麼？
-What? -The flirting.
什麼？ 打情罵俏
Aren't you supposed to be going out with, let's see, my sister?
你不是正要去… 跟誰來著… 我妹妹約會？
I wasn't flirting.
我沒在打情罵俏啊
It was totally flirting! "Somebody got a haircut...."
那根本就是打情罵俏 「新髮型喔」
First of all, the impression? Uncanny.
好，第一件事 你模仿得很蹩腳
Second, that wasn't flirting. That was just casual conversation.
第二，那不是打情罵俏 只是兩個人閒話家常而已
Yeah, right.
我聽你在說
You wanna see flirting? I'll show you.
你要看打情罵俏？ 我示範給你看
I'm good.
不用了
The One Where Ross Can't Flirt
本集播出：「調情遜手」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
I am so proud of Joey.
我真替喬伊感到驕傲
-He's gonna be on Law and Order! -I know.
他竟然要演「法網游龍」 我知道
Don't you think it should be called Order and Law?
可是你不覺得 叫「網法游龍」比較對嗎？
No,because they arrest the guy and then try him.
不對，得先有法律才能去網啊
Don't get me started on that.
我話匣子一開可就沒完了
-I was not flirting. -And on your anniversary. For shame!
我沒在打情罵俏 還在紀念日當天，丟臉！
What's going on?
怎麼了？
He was hitting on the hot delivery girl.
錢德跟外送辣妹打情罵俏
I was not. And oh, God!
我才沒有，拜託你也小聲點
You were. If anyone should be hitting on her...
有就是有 而且就算有誰跟要她搭訕
...it's the guy who's single...
也應該是單身的男人
...the guy who can do something about it.
也應該是有搞頭的人嘛
Sounds like someone wants to be Mr. Pizza Delivery Girl.
看來有人想把比薩外送妹了
Is that what this is about? You like Caitlin?
原來是這樣？你喜歡凱特琳？
Ross, we broke up two years ago. You've been married since then.
羅斯，我們分手都兩年了  中間你還結過婚
I think it's okay that we see other people.
我們各自約會應該沒問題吧
I was watching her at the pizza place.
我前幾天在比薩店看到她
And she was just so sexy and funny and has the cutest little
她性感又風趣… 還有小巧可愛的…
We don't need her measurements.
三圍不用說了
Pepperoni,pepperoni,pepperoni.
三個都是意大利臘腸比薩
She's pretty and you love her, but is she stupid?
羅斯，我知道她人美你又愛 但她是不是蠢了點？
She forgot my vegetarian.
她忘了我點的素食比薩
This is perfect. She'll have to come back here with your pizza.
太完美了 她一定會回來送你的素食比薩
And when she does, I will turn on the charm "au" Ross.
到時我就展現出羅斯的魅力
I am so glad you don't eat meat.
我真高興你不吃肉
See? Vegetarianism benefits everyone.
看吧，吃素對大家都好
Hey,everybody,look who's here! You remember my grandmother.
大家看是誰來了 還記得我祖母嗎？
-Big night! -Yeah,it's so cool.
太酷了
Joey on Law and Order. You must be proud.
喬伊參與「法網游龍」演出 你一定很驕傲吧
She doesn't understand a word of English.
錢德，她完全聽不懂英文
I thought you were Joey's other grandmother.
抱歉，我以為你是喬伊的阿媽
I've done it again.
我還猛說英文
Nonnie's my biggest fan.
她是我的頭號影迷
She's the only one in the family who's always believed in me.
家族裡只有她一個 從頭到尾都相信我
Si. Big star.
對，他是大明星
My big fat Joey star.
我的胖胖喬伊大明星
Yeah,I weighed,like, 27 pounds when I was born.
對，我出生是27磅，所以…
-Happy anniversary! -Happy anniversary,10 months.
紀念日快樂 十個月紀念日快樂
In the shower I was thinking about our first night in London.
我剛才在淋浴的時候 想起我們在倫敦的第一晚
Joey's grandmother's right there.
喬伊的祖母來了
-The one who speaks English? -The one who doesn't.
會說英文的還是不會的那個？ 不會的那個
That was some hot love you gave me.
那晚你給的愛還真是火熱
-I'll get ready. -Wear those earrings I got you.
我去準備一下 不如戴我送你的耳環？
That's a great idea. I was saving them for something special.
好主意，就是要留到特別場合 好
-You've got to go home. -But I like it here.
你得回家去 但是我喜歡這裡啊
Get the earrings you borrowed. He wants me to wear them.
你得回家拿我借你的耳環 錢德要我今晚戴那副耳環
I think they're in my purse. Go get dressed and I'll look for them.
好，應該是放在我皮包裡 你去穿衣服，我去找 好
I need those earrings you borrowed.
瑞秋，我要拿回我借你的耳環
Yeah,I'll be right back.
好，我馬上回來
Phoebe,you speak ltalian?
菲比，你會說意大利文？
I guess so.
我猜是吧
-Here you go. -Thanks. Where's the other one?
來，謝謝你 等等 另外一個呢？
Oh,what, you want both of them? That's a little greedy, don't you think?
你兩個都要？ 會不會太貪心了？
Rachel Karen Greene, where's the other one?
瑞秋葛林，另一個耳環呢？
Look, just don't freak out, but I kind of lost it.
好啦，你先別生氣 好像不見了
I know it's in the apartment, but I definitely lost it.
還在公寓裡，但一定不見了
What'll I tell Monica? She wants to wear them tonight.
那我要怎麼跟摩妮卡說？ 她今晚就要戴
-Tell her to wear her own earrings. -These are her earrings.
叫她戴自己的耳環 這就是她的耳環
不會吧…
You lent me her earrings? I'm not allowed to borrow her stuff!
你把摩妮卡的耳環借我？ 我不能借她的東西耶
-Why not? -Because I lose her stuff!
為什麼？ 因為我都會弄丟
You see that blind guy? I'm gonna bash his head in later.
看到那個盲人沒？ 我等一下會痛打他一頓
My big scene's coming up. The big scene coming up.
我的主戲就快來了 主戲就快來了
If you said, "Big lima bean bubbling up," would she know the difference?
若你說「吃葡萄不吐葡萄皮」 她會不會比較懂？
What are you doing?
瑞秋，你在幹嘛？
Oh, I just can't watch. It's too scary.
我不敢看，太恐怖了
It's a diaper commercial.
現在是賣尿布的廣告
Yeah,well,you know me. Babies,responsibilities....
你也知道我的 小孩啊，責任，嚇死人
-Pizza delivery. -I'll get it! I will get that!
比薩外送 我來開 我來拿
How does my hair look?
我的髮型如何？
Ross,it hasn't moved since 1996.
羅斯，你從96年就沒變過了
One vegetarian pizza. It's 12.50.
一個素食比薩 12.5美元
By the way,if it makes you feel any better...
對了，如果這會讓你好過些
...I happen to like 8-year-old boys.
我正好很喜歡八歲男孩
What?
什麼？
Your hair. Before. Your hair.
你的頭髮 之前你說過
You said you thought your hair looked like an 8-year-old boy's...
你的髮型很像八歲男孩
...and I'm just saying I like it.
我說我很喜歡…
The hair.
你的髮型
Thanks.
謝謝
You understand,I don't actually like 8-year-old boys.
我不是真的喜歡八歲男孩
All I'm looking for is the money.
我在等你找錢
Here you go. Stop bringing us pizzas,you.
這裡 別再幫我們送比薩了
I'm gonna try.
我都快哭了
You're welcome.
不客氣
You couldn't let me have her, could you?
你就是不想看我得手，對吧？
This is a girl I really like, and you had to swoop in there!
什麼？我真的很喜歡這個女孩 你幹嘛要來湊熱鬧？
What?
怎麼了？
Chandler was flirting with the hot delivery girl.
錢德衝著外送辣妹打情罵俏
Thank you for that.
真是多謝你了
I was not flirting.
我沒有打情罵俏
It's okay. I don't care. That's fine.
沒關係，我不在意，無所謂
Really?
什麼？ 真的？
It's no big deal. I do it all the time.
小事一件，我動不動也是
You flirt with guys all the time?
你動不動就跟人打情罵俏？
It doesn't mean anything. Just like it doesn't mean anything with you.
是啊，那又不代表什麼 你不是也沒別的意思
There's a difference. You're a lot hotter.
對，但是有一點很不一樣 你比我辣多了
True story.
這是真的
This actually bothers you?
錢德，你真的介意？
Yes, and I think it'd bother a lot of people.
對，我是介意 我想很多人都會介意
When you and Ross dated...
瑞秋，你和羅斯在一起那時
...did it bother you when he flirted with other women?
他跟別的女人打情罵俏 你會不會介意？
No,it bothered me when he slept with other women.
不會…他跟別的女人上床 我才會介意
And thank you for that.
真是多謝了
I never had to worry.
但其實我沒啥好擔心的
He was never good at the flirting thing.
羅斯從來就不太會打情罵俏
What?
什麼？…
What are you talking about? It worked with you.
你在說什麼？對你不就有效
No, you're right.
你說的真是對極了
We met,you flirted and then bam! Nine years later, you had me.
我們認識，你對我打情罵俏 九年後你終於追到我了
All right.
好…
You know what I'll do? I'll order another pizza.
就這麼辦 我再來點個比薩
And when Caitlin gets here...
等凱特琳來的時候
...I will show you how well I flirt.
我就來讓你們見識一下 我有多會打情罵俏
I will get her phone number.
我還能要到她的電話號碼
And not the one on the menu.
不是比薩店的電話啦
-I found it. -Thank God! Where was it?
我找到了 謝天謝地，在哪裡找到的？
On your dresser.
在你的梳妝台上
Okay, that is the one we already have.
那是原來的那一個
Here's my big scene. My big scene's here.
我的主戲到了，就是現在
-Wanna bet nobody heard anything? -No bet.
Anybody home?
有人在嗎？
-Oh,my God. -What?
天啊 幹嘛？
Everybody keep smiling. It'll kill my grandmother if she finds out.
大家繼續笑 我祖母發現一定會難過到死掉
What is it?
怎麼了？
They cut me out of the show.
我那一段被剪掉了
What?
什麼？
-Are you sure? -Maybe your scene's coming up.
你確定？ 或許現在才輪到你上
Not likely. Because you see that body bag right there?
不太可能 看到那個裝屍體的袋子沒？
I'm in it.
有啊 裡頭裝的是我
This is terrible. What'll you do?
太糟糕了，你要怎麼辦？
I don't know. This little old lady lives for my career.
不知道 我的老祖母活著 就是為了看我演戲
When they dumped me off Days of Our Lives,she almost died.
上回「我們的日子」不要我 她差點難過到死掉
That's not good.
那樣很不妙
-Yeah,we had to get her a home nurse. -Oh,my God.
我們還找了個特別看護來照顧她 天啊
Yeah, she almost died and got really expensive.
她差點死掉 還花了我們好多錢
You're not smiling. Not that face! Everybody smile!
別用那種表情，大家繼續笑…
Just tell her what happened. It's not your fault.
喬伊，你怎麼不實話實說？ 那又不能怪你
If we keep talking this way, won't we freak her out soon?
如果我們繼續這樣說話 會不會嚇到她？
Soon. I'm gonna be on soon.
很快…馬上就輪我上場了
There I am!
那就是我！
Sam Waterston!
山姆瓦特斯頓！
No,no. That's me. That's me!
不對…那是我…
No. Sam Waterston.
不是，那是山姆瓦特斯頓
Crime Misdemeanor, Capricorn One.
「愛與罪」 「摩羯一號大行動」
She doesn't know "hello," but she knows Capricorn One.
她聽不懂「你好」 卻知道「摩羯一號大行動」
I need those earrings. We're leaving when the show's over.
菲比，我要那副耳環了 節目一演完我們就要出去
But I already gave them back to you.
可是我已經還你了啊
No,you didn't.
才沒有
I already didn't gave them back to you. That's what I said.
好，我已經還沒還給你 我就是這樣說的啊
Where's that other earring?
另一個耳環在哪裡？
It's not here,Phoebe. It's not here.
菲比，不在這裡…
I went to Chandler's last night.
我昨晚有去錢德和喬伊那裡
Make sure you check Chandler's jewelry box.
好，記得要檢查錢德的珠寶盒
Chandler has a jewelry box?
慢著，錢德有珠寶盒？
We have 10 minutes. Do you want me to get into that now?
好了，時間緊迫 你要我現在就跟你解釋？
Hey,Phoebe.
菲比
How's that...
那個...
...vegetarian pizza working out for you?
素食比薩… 你吃得還習慣嗎？
You and those vegetables have a real...
你和那些蔬菜
...thing going on,huh?
還真是有兩下子，是吧？
Why are you being weird?
你幹嘛怪裡怪氣的？
Do you like it?
你喜不喜歡？
No. That'd be, "Why are you being cute?"
不喜歡，否則我就會問 「你幹嘛裝可愛」了
Okay. I'm working on my flirting.
好吧，我在練習打情罵俏
I did not get that.
原來如此，我沒看出來
So, Monica, do you like Law and Order?
摩妮卡，你喜歡看 「法網游龍」嗎？
Yeah,it's good.
喜歡，很好看
I found out all this stuff about you. You like Law and Order...
我今天發現到了新的你 好比你愛看「法網游龍」
...and you've flirted with every guy in the tri-state area.
還有你到處跟人打情罵俏
Okay,let me get this straight.
好，我來問個清楚
It's okay for you to flirt, but not for me?
你可以打情罵俏，我卻不行
I'm glad we cleared that up.
真高興我們把話說清楚了
I'm sorry, but some things are different for men and women.
抱歉，但你聽我說 男女有些事是不一樣的
Teach me about men and women.
繼續，開釋我一些男女的差別
I've already taught you so much already, but whatever.
好，雖然我已經教過你很多了
When you flirt with a guy, you think,"No big deal."
你跟男人打情罵俏的時候 你覺得只是打情罵俏 沒啥大不了的
But he thinks,"Finally! Somebody who wants to sleep with me."
但對方會覺得 他終於找到人上床了
-No way! -It's true.
不可能 這是真的
-Well,that's pathetic. -Again,true.
真可悲 這也是真的
-This goes for all guys? -All guys that are awake.
男人都這樣嗎？ 醒著的男人都適用
We go to sleep.
等我們上床睡覺後
All guys from the other end of the world wake up and act the same way.
世界另一邊的男人起床 繼續做一模一樣的事
It's another commercial and I still haven't told her.
好，又進廣告了 我還是沒跟她說
Joey,this is the last commercial.
喬伊，這是最後一段廣告
-You got 10 minutes left. -I know!
你只剩十分鐘了 我知道…
What am I gonna do?
你要我怎麼辦？
You will not run out and leave her here.
不許你落跑，留她在這裡
Yeah,all right.
對，好啦
喬伊？
Joey's gonna be right back. Right back?
喬伊馬上回來 馬上回來？
Meanwhile,let's talk about you.
我們順便來聊聊你吧
So you're old and small.
你年紀大，個子小
-Did you find it? -The earring,no.
找到沒？ 耳環是沒有
But I found my sunglasses.
但我在沙發底下 找到我的太陽眼鏡
I've been looking for these since last summer.
我從去年夏天找到現在
Those are mine. You borrowed them from me.
那是我借你的太陽眼鏡
Okay. Calm down. Here they are.
好，別激動，還你就是了
菲比
-What do we do? -I don't know. I don't know!
我們要怎麼辦？ 我不知道…
We'll just have to tell Monica,that's all.
我們只好老實跟摩妮卡說了
Oh,God! She's gonna kill me.
老天，她一定會殺了我
I could tell her it was all my fault.
我可以跟她說是我弄掉的
Oh,that'd be great.
那就太好了
Mon, could I talk to you?
摩妮卡，我有話要跟你說
Yeah. What is it?
好，什麼事？
I lost one of your earrings.
我弄丟了你一支耳環
I'm sorry. I am so,so sorry.
對不起，我真的很抱歉
All right,what can you do? If you lost it, you lost it.
好吧，都弄丟了還能怎樣
I'll replace it. I promise. I feel so terrible.
我保證會賠你一副新的 我真的很愧疚
That's fine. You didn't do it on purpose.
沒關係，你又不是故意的
Look at you. Come here.
瞧你難過的，來
-You feel better? -Yeah. You're the best.
好點了沒？ 有啊，你最棒了
Okay, wait a minute.
好，等一等
I can't do this.
我不能這樣
Listen, honey, it's not Phoebe's fault.
其實不是菲比弄丟的
She lent me the earrings.
她把你的耳環借我
I lost it. I'm so sorry,honey. I feel terrible too.
是我弄丟的，我真的很抱歉 我也覺得好愧疚
That is exactly why I do not lend you stuff!
所以我才不借你東西！
First,my jewelry. If it's not that,it's my sweater.
先是我的首飾 不是首飾，就是我的藍色毛衣
And if it's not that, it's my sunglasses.
不是藍色毛衣 就是我的太陽眼鏡
-Your sunglasses? -Yes！
你的太陽眼鏡？ 對！
Oh,right.
對耶
-Pizza. -Mine,mine,mine!
比薩外送 我的！…
Okay,here goes.
好，要開始了
Prepare yourselves for some class-A flirting.
準備見識一流的打情罵俏
Okay,hold on.
等等…
Okay.
我準備好了
You have nothing to prove.And if you really like this girl, I don't think flirting is the right way
你犯不著這樣 若你真的喜歡這個女孩 我也不覺得打情罵俏是…
You'll see. Okay.
等著看就知道，好吧
What's her name?
她叫什麼名字？
Caitlin!
凱特琳…
We can't keep eating like this.
這樣吃下去也不是辦法
It's $12.50.
12.5美元
Okay.
好
Do you make the pizzas in one of those wood-burning ovens?
你們做比薩 是用燒木頭的爐子嗎？
No,actually,I think they're gas.
不是，其實是瓦斯爐
Gas?
瓦斯爐？
Intense.
真帶勁
If this is how all the Gellers flirt, we don't have a problem.
如果蓋勒家的人 都這樣打情罵俏的話 我們就沒有問題了
You know that smell gas has?
你知道瓦斯的味道嗎？
-Yeah. -They put that in.
知道 那是加進去的
-What? -The gas is odorless.
什麼？ 瓦斯其實是無色無味
But they add the smell so you know when there's a leak.
加上味道是為了讓人 在瓦斯漏氣時能聞得出來
Well,okay.
好吧
A lot of other gas smells.
很多氣體都有味道…
Oh,the humanity!
救命喔
Methane smells....
甲烷有味道…
You know what? Actually, I really should go.
不好意思，我真的得走了
-But I haven't paid you yet. -That's okay.
我還沒付錢呢 沒關係
You guys have ordered so many that this one's on me.
你們點了那麼多 這一個算我請的
Was I talking to her about gas?
我是不是跟她說到瓦斯的事？
More so than anything else.
那根本就是主題
I found it interesting.
我覺得很有意思
I'm sorry. No.
我很遺憾 不用…
Don't worry about it.
別擔心
In nine years,she and l will be right there!
九年之後 我和她就能在一起了
I'm gonna clear out some of these boxes.
好，我去清掉這些比薩盒
-Ross? -Yeah? -What else do they add smell to?
羅斯？ 怎麼了？ 還有哪些氣體會加味道？
Caitlin! Caitlin!
Hi,I'm Rachel.
我是瑞秋
From upstairs? The ones with all the pizza?
住樓上的 叫一堆比薩的那家
Was there a problem?
比薩有問題嗎？
No,they're fine. Great pizza.
不是…比薩很好吃
But,actually,my friend Ross...
其實是我朋友羅斯的事
...he gets nervous when he's flirting.
他只要打情罵俏就會緊張
Oh,my God!
天啊
-That was flirting? -Yeah.
他是在打情罵俏？ 沒錯
I know,I know.
我知道你的感覺…
I'm telling you, once you get past that part...
不過一旦過了那個階段
...where it feels like you wanna die...
那個讓你想要自殺的階段
...he's a really good person.
你就會發現他是個大好人
The guy with the gas?
開口閉口都是瓦斯的那個人？
I'm telling you,he's really sweet and really funny...
他真的很體貼風趣
...and he's just got a good heart.
還有一副好心腸
You know,actually,I did think that he was cute and then he started talking.
其實我覺得他蠻可愛的 可是一開始說話就…
See,there you go.
這就對了…
-Besides, I think he really likes you. -Really?
而且我覺得他很喜歡你 真的嗎？
Well,we have seven people and 10 pizzas. What do you think?
我們七個人，卻叫了十個比薩 這還不夠明顯嗎？
I thought Joey was there.
我想說喬伊很會吃
Yeah, no, but just I'm telling you he's worth a shot.
羅斯值得你去試試看
Well, if he's so great why don't you go out with him?
如果他那麼棒 你怎麼不去跟他約會？
Well,you know,at some point...
你知道嗎？ 有朝一日...
...you and I may need to have a longer conversation.
...我們可能需要好好聊一聊
Hey, Ross?
羅斯？
I just ran into Caitlin in the hallway.
我剛才在走廊遇到凱特琳
You must be getting better at this flirting stuff than I thought.
你打情罵俏的技巧 肯定比我想像中更高明
-What? -I don't get it,but she wanted me...
什麼意思？ 雖然我搞不懂
...to give you her number.
但她要我轉交她的電話給你
And she just gave you this?
她自己給你的？
Rach, thanks. But I don't need you doing me any favors.
瑞秋，謝了 但我不需要你幫忙
I didn't. She thought you were cute.
我沒幫忙啊，是她覺得你可愛
Well,that I can believe.
這點我倒是相信
Hey,is the show still on?
還在演嗎？
Almost over,man.
快要演完了
Hey,Nonnie.
Is that the pope?
那是教宗嗎？
Why am I looking?
我幹嘛跟過去看？
Oh, here I am! This is my big scene.
來了，我的主戲上場
All right, back off!
快退後
I got a gun!
我有槍喔
I'm not afraid to use it.
用起來可不會手軟
-Joey! That's right, Nonnie.
喬伊！
You couldn't have at least changed your shirt?
你起碼也該換一件上衣的
Now, I want a suitcase filled with $ 100,000
我要你在手提箱裡 裝滿十萬美元…
Filled with $ 100,000 in small bills.
裝滿十萬美元的小鈔
And if I don't get Shoo!
若是我沒拿到…
And if I don't get it...
...I'll shoot this duck!
我就斃了這支鴨子
Oh,no!
不能這樣
I'm coming out!
我要出去了
And she's supposed to buy this?
她會相信嗎？
Joey, bravo!
喬伊，太棒了！…
Ground control to Major Tom
地面控制隊呼叫總部…
Commencing countdown
倒數開始…
Engines
動力…
On
全開
That's scenes from next week's show. Next week.
這是下周的片段…下周的
I am definitely gonna watch that.
我一定要等著看
Do these look the same?
這一副呢？看起來一樣嗎？
-Definitely. -Not as each other.
一模一樣 是分開來看
Then,no.
不 那就不一樣了
-Hey,you ready? -Yeah.
準備好了麼？ 好了
You look amazing. I'm the luckiest man in the world.
你真美 我是全世界最幸運的男人
You're about to get a little luckier.
你即將要更幸運了
-Let me see the earrings. -Right,the earrings.
耳環讓我看看 耳環…
They look great.
美極了
Does your boyfriend have the best taste or what?
你男友真是品味一流呢
My boyfriend really does have great taste.
我男友的品味真的很棒
Thanks for picking out the earrings.
多謝你幫我選耳環